When working with data within
spreadsheets, you will more than likely
need to apply some sort of numerical
formatting and number formatting
to the data within the spreadsheet.
And as you can see at the moment,
all we have here is all of the
information, numerical information
is just in general format.
And as you can see, we have the price
and the total income columns, which
really should be in a financial format.
So to change a column or a selection
of data into financial format.
All I'm simply going to do is click
on B, go to the number section
of the home tab, select currency.
And that will change that to currency.
Similarly, for the total income,
I'll go down and select currency.
So that has applied that to that column.
So anything else that is entered into that
column, so if additional rows are added
for other offers within the organization,
it would automatically format
anything in that column as currency.
There is also some information here
in the average sales row which has
got numbers after a decimal point.
Now, as the average sales should be
actual whole numbers, because you
won't have 0.2 of a sale or 0.6 of
a sale, what you can do, if you have
information that is showing a decimal
point and then some information after
that, you can reduce that if you
need to show it as whole numbers.
If you wish to have it as a decimal point
in the information shown that's fine,
but for this, it should be whole numbers.
So what I'll do is I've just
selected all of the data in that
row by clicking and dragging along.
And if you look on the number
section there, you can see there's an
increase and decrease decimal option.
So what I need to do is I need
to select the decrease decimals.
And if I just click on that.
They have all been taken
down to whole numbers.
Again, if I had some information, that
I want to show more decimal places,
I can actually just increase it by
clicking on that button there, but I'll
take this back down to whole numbers.